xlr8r.com 2018-02-01

# Privacy Policy (Ticketing) – XLR8R

When you use the XLR8R site, you are consenting to the practices set forth in the below Privacy Policy Guidelines.

**Your IP Address**

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer the Site. Your IP address is also used to help identify you and to gather broad demographic information about you. Your IP address may also be used to assist in the detection of fraud and we may pass this information to the police.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a small file that is automatically issued to your computer when you enter our Site and which is stored by the browser on your computer's hard drive. Cookies identify your computer, not the individual user of your computer. Cookies store some basic information that helps us to identify if a user of your computer has visited the Site before and if you have provided us with some personalized information. Our Site uses cookies to keep track of what you have purchased. We use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests, to save your password (if you have supplied us with one) so you do not have to re-enter it each time you visit our Site, and for other purposes, such as informing you that you may have made multiple bookings for specific events on our Site. You can disable cookies or set your browser to alert you when cookies are being sent, but if you choose to do so you may not be able to access some areas of the Site.

**Information We Require From You**

Our Site's registration forms, order forms, surveys, competitions and prize draws require you to give us personal information (like your name, address and/or email address). XLR8R does not store any financial information, if you are ordering tickets to an event, you will be asked to provide financial information to Paypal by Paypal, and not by XLR8R.com.

**How XLR8R Will Use Your Personal Information?**

As a ticket agent, XLR8R sells tickets on behalf of the venue or promoter that produces the event for which you buy a ticket. We refer to the venue or promoter from whom we obtain tickets to sell to you as our "Event Partner". Your personal information is shared between XLR8R and its Event Partner for the particular event for which you are buying tickets in accordance with this Privacy Policy and XLR8R's contractual relationship with its Event Partner.

Your personal information is used by us to contact you by email, post, or phone, when necessary in connection with transactions entered into by you via the Site.

**Disclosure of Your Personal Information in Compliance with Laws**

You should be aware that we may release your personal information when we believe it is necessary to comply with laws or regulations, to assist law enforcement, to enforce the terms under which you transacted with XLR8R, or to protect the rights, property or safety of XLR8R, users of the Site or others.

**Transfer of Personal Information in Event of Sale of XLR8R**

In the event that XLR8R is sold, or transferred some of its assets to another party, your personal information could be one of the transferred assets. If your personal information is transferred, use of your personal information will remain subject to this Privacy Policy. Your personal information will be passed on to a successor in interest in the event of a liquidation or administration of XLR8R.

This Site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. We use 128 bit industry standard Secure Server Software (SSL) for your transactions with us. It encrypts all of your personal information, name, and address, so that it cannot be read as the information travels over the Internet.
